what time kind of time zone they are at and what kind of daily spend they are at.
他们处于哪个时区的时间以及他们的日常支出是怎样的。
So in this example all you need to do is to multiply this spending pattern in
因此，在这个例子中，您需要做的就是将这个支出模式乘以
this day by 365 to identify what the year looks like. So we mapped out the we
这一天通过 365 来确定这一年是什么样子。所以我们制定了我们
mapped out and extrapolated the spending habits and you can see that from Monday
绘制并推断消费习惯，从周一开始你就可以看到
to Sunday the heat map will show you the green squares where they spend the least
到周日，热图将向您显示他们花费最少的绿色方块
amount of money at different time intervals and then the red squares
不同时间间隔的金额，然后是红色方块
will show you where the most amount of money is spent at and what interval and
会告诉你最多的钱花在哪里以及什么时间间隔和
you can also identify the monthly spending habits such as subscriptions or
您还可以确定每月的消费习惯，例如订阅或
even yearly month yearly spending habits and to take this step even further your
甚至每年每月每年的消费习惯，并进一步采取这一步
income is public too. How you top up your card is also public too. Profiling
收入也是公开的。您如何为卡充值也是公开的。分析
3,500 people all at once you can identify what kind of users actually use
一次性3500人你可以识别出什么样的用户实际使用
the NoSysPay card and we found that 4% are high rollers which is they spend
NoSysPay 卡，我们发现 4% 是豪赌客，他们花的钱
more than 5,000 euros a month and then 22% are daily spenders. So using
每月消费超过 5,000 欧元，其中 22% 是日常消费。所以使用
simple queries like this you can gather massive amount of information and most
像这样的简单查询，您可以收集大量信息，并且大多数
importantly competitive intelligence. This is extremely useful for data
重要的是竞争情报。这对于数据非常有用
indexing companies, really useful for card companies, card competitors you know
索引公司，对卡公司、你知道的卡竞争对手非常有用
it could be EtherFi and how you can actually ensure that your on-chain
它可能是 EtherFi 以及如何确保您的链上
transactions are more private is through our protocol which is privacy pools. So
通过我们的隐私池协议，交易更加私密。所以
at this moment you could use privacy pools it's live on privacypools.com and
此时您可以使用 Privacy Pools.com 上的隐私池，并且
how privacy pools enable your privacy is through zero knowledge proofs to break
隐私池如何让你的隐私通过零知识证明来破解
the link between deposits and withdrawals. I'm sorry I need to play the
存款和取款之间的联系。抱歉，我需要玩
video yeah so in this demo you can create a ZK wallet on privacy pools you
视频 是的，所以在这个演示中，您可以在您的隐私池上创建一个 ZK 钱包
can select the chain and deposit any amount from your wallet. The deposit is
可以选择链并从钱包中存入任何金额。押金是
reviewed by Oxbow's association set provider and when we determine that your
由 Oxbow 协会套件提供商审核，并且当我们确定您的
deposits are not affiliated with any threat actors you are free to withdraw it
存款与任何威胁行为者无关，您可以自由提取
in any amount to a clean wallet such as topping up your card. So using our
任意金额存入干净的钱包，例如为您的卡充值。所以使用我们的
protocol it actually breaks the link between where your money comes from to
它实际上打破了你的资金来源与资金来源之间的联系
how you spend it and the most exciting part which is today I'm going to share
你是如何度过的以及今天我要分享的最令人兴奋的部分
with you upgraded features of privacy pools. So at our new upgrade which is
与您一起升级隐私池功能。所以在我们的新升级中
coming soon will enable users to make private transfers to a private vault so
即将推出的功能将使用户能够进行私人转账到私人保险库，以便
nobody sees anything and we will basically enable Venmo style payments.
没有人看到任何东西，我们基本上将启用 Venmo 风格的支付。
What I mean by that is this. Sorry the video function is not working. I'm so
我的意思是这样的。抱歉，视频功能无法使用。我就是这样
sorry I I am not sure why the video function is not working so let me just
抱歉，我不知道为什么视频功能不起作用，所以让我说一下
describe it. So instead of let's give a round plus for the for the privacy pools
描述它。因此，我们不要为隐私池加一轮
oh okay sorry yeah yes so so you can send privately and you can ask for
哦，好吧，抱歉，是的，所以你可以私下发送，你可以要求
payment and it's a Venmo style payment portal you can ask and request for
付款，这是一个 Venmo 风格的付款门户，您可以询问和请求
payments from anybody you don't if you ask your friend for a payment you don't
如果您向您的朋友索要一笔您没有收到的款项，则来自任何您不知情的人的付款
need their wallet address and you pay someone they don't really need your
需要他们的钱包地址，而你付钱给他们并不真正需要你的人
wallet address so we enable double-blind payments. I'm sorry the time is up but
钱包地址，以便我们启用双盲付款。抱歉，时间到了，但是
if you want to know about privacy pools you can come and find me later. Privacy
如果你想了解隐私池可以稍后来找我。隐私
pools, privacy is for everyone. We're also working with the Ethereum Foundation
泳池，隐私属于每个人。我们还与以太坊基金会合作
to enable private transactions for everyone on chain. Thank you. Thank you
为链上的每个人提供私人交易。谢谢。谢谢
privacy pools. Having seen all these innovative projects building on Ethereum
隐私池。看过所有这些建立在以太坊上的创新项目
it's clear that the ecosystem is thriving. Our next speaker Audrey Tong
很明显，生态系统正在蓬勃发展。我们的下一位演讲者 Audrey Tong
executive director of EAG will share her insights on towards real-world
EAG执行董事将分享她对现实世界的见解
applications. Please welcome Audrey. Hello I think it has been half the day and we
应用程序。请欢迎奥黛丽。你好，我想已经过去半天了，我们
could see a lot of the gainer, we could see lots of the website chat and a lot
可以看到很多获胜者，我们可以看到很多网站聊天和很多
of the demos was just a present and I think of you have the one question in
演示只是一份礼物，我想您有一个问题
mind what is EAG and this time I think it's let me introduce more about what
介意什么是 EAG，这次我想让我介绍更多关于什么
is EAG actually is and what is EAG came from. So what is EAG? EAG is from builders
EAG 实际上是，EAG 是从何而来。那么什么是EAG呢？ EAG来自建筑商
and for builders and for EAG it's from the long-term Ethereum holders builders
对于建设者和 EAG 来说，它来自长期持有以太坊的建设者
which is have been supporting the Ethereum community for over decades from
数十年来一直支持以太坊社区
the day one of the ether midnight towards the nowadays and from I think for
从以太午夜到今天的第一天，从我想
the last 10 years it's more for the infrastructure but towards the future
过去十年更多的是基础设施，但面向未来
of the application world we need to accelerate the applications more so this
在应用程序世界中，我们需要进一步加速应用程序，因此这
is the main idea that the EAG well came from and the original concept and the
是 EAG well 的主要思想以及最初的概念和
supporters is from the 10 over 10 years Ethereum builders and also there are lots
支持者来自 10 多年的以太坊建设者，而且还有很多
of the question that we figured out from the what's the past three years doing the
我们从过去三年所做的事情中找出的问题
Shanghai Wu which is also a public city around the world and for we started the
上海吴也是世界各地的一个公共城市，因此我们开始了
Shanghai Wu in about the 2023 and at that time because of for the Asia
上海吴大约在2023年，当时因为对于亚洲
Ethereum community there are lack of exchange and the lack of communication
Ethereum community there are lack of exchange and the lack of communication
and during for the first year of Shanghai Wu we bring the main Asia
在上海吴的第一年，我们带来了主要的亚洲
community and the developer Ethereum builders together in Beidahu to discuss
社区与开发者以太坊建设者们齐聚北大湖共同探讨
what we could do for the Ethereum community and then later at about two
我们可以为以太坊社区做些什么，然后在大约两点
years ago someone asked us because you know at that time in about 2024 at that
几年前有人问我们，因为你知道当时大约是 2024 年
time the DIPCOM Bangkok was decided to host in Bangkok so at that time earlier
DIPCOM 曼谷会议决定在曼谷举办，所以当时时间较早
that year and someone asked us that okay well you know the
那一年，有人问我们，好吧，你知道
Shanghai Wu would be like to host the public city again in Chiang Mai just before the
上海吴希望在清迈举办公共城市活动之前再次举办
DIPCOM that's why during the October of the 2024 lots of the public cities in
DIPCOM 这就是为什么在 2024 年 10 月期间，许多公共城市
there you could see there is a public city season in Chiang Mai just before
在那里你可以看到清迈之前有一个公共城市季节
DIPCOM and at that time lots of the it's not only for Asia builders but for
DIPCOM，当时很多不仅是针对亚洲建筑商，而且是针对
the whole global builders in the Ethereum ecosystem we collaborate we
我们与以太坊生态系统中的所有全球建设者合作
exchange a lot communicate a lot that's how could we support a better
exchange a lot communicate a lot that's how could we support a better
communication and to support the Ethereum community in Asia together and
沟通并共同支持亚洲的以太坊社区
also during that time we found that you know for public cities there are lots of
also during that time we found that you know for public cities there are lots of
the builders in there lots of the good ideas on the early stage testing there
那里的建设者在早期测试中有很多好主意
but there are but some of them are still very struggling because some of them
但有些人仍然很挣扎，因为有些人
develop some open source tools and have the struggle with the fundraising
开发一些开源工具并在筹款中遇到困难
sustainable issue so during that time we are trying to bring all the VCs to
可持续发展问题所以在那段时间我们正在努力让所有风险投资人
Chiang Mai to have the demo day for the builders that they could direct the pitch
清迈将为建筑商举办演示日，让他们可以指导球场
for VCs and to communicate with VCs and to have the results and but later we
for VCs and to communicate with VCs and to have the results and but later we
figured out that it's not enough for just doing one demo day or one pitch day
发现仅仅进行一个演示日或一个推介日是不够的
there are still lots of a gap between the individual builders to a more
there are still lots of a gap between the individual builders to a more
mature project yeah so during that time we are trying to establish and help
mature project yeah so during that time we are trying to establish and help
builders more about it so that is the third year of Shanghai WUM which was the
建筑商对此进行了更多了解，所以今年是上海 WUM 的第三年，这是
location in Singapore because of the resources the founders the funding the
location in Singapore because of the resources the founders the funding the
resources are located in Singapore and we also want to bring the 10 globally to
resources are located in Singapore and we also want to bring the 10 globally to
Singapore but the Singapore of you know it's very expensive so we also gave lots
新加坡但是你们知道新加坡很贵所以我们也给了很多
of the scholarships for the builders from the Africa Latin America Australia
of the scholarships for the builders from the Africa Latin America Australia
Indian to bring them together to build something during that time so for 30
Indian to bring them together to build something during that time so for 30
year of Shanghai were in the evolving a lot from the traditional public city or
year of Shanghai were in the evolving a lot from the traditional public city or
concept test to a more mature way to help builders from individual to show
concept test to a more mature way to help builders from individual to show
mature project so during that time we invite lots of the VCs and the founders
mature project so during that time we invite lots of the VCs and the founders
to tell them their experience and what does they really want to know as when
to tell them their experience and what does they really want to know as when
they when they start their business and tell the and let the VCs to told the
they when they start their business and tell the and let the VCs to told the
developers the builders how could they have the sustainable fund their PMF or
开发商、建筑商如何才能拥有可持续发展基金、PMF 或
to pitch with VCs or to do fundraising yeah so it's more like more like we
与风险投资公司合作或进行筹款是的，所以这更像是我们
it's more like the accelerator but it's more for the builders from the whole
它更像是加速器，但更适合整个建设者
ecosystem so what we found in last three years is that although or what we have
生态系统所以我们在过去三年中发现的是，尽管或我们拥有什么
done in Singapore where it's more like the accelerator but it's still not
在新加坡完成，那里更像是加速器，但仍然不是
enough there are still lots of gaps from the individual builder to became the
足够了，从个体建设者到成为
succeed project so just like if you being the individual builder at first
成功的项目就像你一开始是个人建造者一样
that way we need a lot of the education no matter from the community side and
that way we need a lot of the education no matter from the community side and
lots of the local community no matter the Chinese-speaking community the
很多当地社区，无论是华语社区还是
Thailand community Latin America community Africa community doing a lot
泰国社区 拉丁美洲社区 非洲社区 做了很多
of jobs to educate the developers and help the project grow but lots of the
教育开发人员并帮助项目发展的工作岗位，但很多
communities do very struggle with the sustainable issue because yeah and so
社区确实在可持续问题上非常挣扎，因为是的，所以
lots of the public goods are struggle so also for the individual builders if you
许多公共物品都在挣扎，对于个体建设者来说也是如此，如果你
want to be more like the no matter the entrepreneur or the project could be
无论企业家还是项目都希望变得更像
succeed there are still lots of the gaps we need to filter and also from the
成功了，我们仍然有很多差距需要过滤，而且还需要从
individual builder nowadays we have lots of the hack zones here but after hack zone just
如今，个人建设者我们这里有很多黑客区域，但在黑客区域之后
when the project of the hack zone what's happened okay we have lots of the
当黑客区的项目发生了什么的时候，我们有很多
missing pieces in the whole life circle of the builders and we need to establish
建设者整个生命周期中缺失的部分，我们需要建立
a sustainable life circle for the builders could grow from the
建设者的可持续生活圈可以从
individual to the project and from the project that if they succeed they also
个人对项目和项目的影响，如果他们成功了，他们也会
could pay get back to the community which helps them a lot in the early stage
could pay get back to the community which helps them a lot in the early stage
so this is what EAG truly came from. EAG is from is a NPO that to bring the
这就是 EAG 的真正来源。 EAG 是一家非营利组织，旨在带来
stakeholders the stakeholders in the Ethereum community together to support
利益相关者 以太坊社区的利益相关者共同支持
and accelerate the Ethereum application ecosystem and what is EAG actually do
并加速以太坊应用生态系统以及EAG实际上在做什么
it's for builders and we gonna do through four passes just like the first
这是为建筑商准备的，我们将像第一个一样完成四遍
thing is to accelerate the real world impact applications and the second is to
一是加速现实世界影响应用，二是
cross the builders network to help builders to help to fill the missing
跨越建筑商网络，帮助建筑商帮助填补缺失
pieces that in the builders life circle and to share the evaluation and develop
构建者生活圈中共享评估和开发的作品
the framework which is also very important because nowadays we are towards
这个框架也非常重要，因为现在我们正在走向
in the future of the applications we want to build the truly depth but not
in the future of the applications we want to build the truly depth but not
instead of just doing what the web applications do. This is how the
而不是只做 Web 应用程序所做的事情。这就是如何
blockchain exists and the how the crypto value exists and also which is also very
区块链的存在以及加密价值如何存在以及这也非常重要
important and the key issue to have the to create a sustainable mechanism to
建立可持续发展机制是当前亟待解决的重要和关键问题
help the public goods grow no matter on the company side on the education side
帮助公共产品成长无论是公司端还是教育端
on each of the open open source tools that will help the whole ecosystem
每个有助于整个生态系统的开源工具
growth. So the operational model for EAG which is it came from the different
生长。所以 EAG 的运营模式来自于不同的
aspect just like a today's event the Ethereum applications gallery is just
就像今天的活动一样，以太坊应用程序库只是
like the whole one day event that helps the audience helps everyone of us know
就像整个一日活动帮助观众帮助我们每个人都知道
what is the recently latest update on the whole Ethereum ecosystem and what
整个以太坊生态系统最近的最新更新是什么？
is the latest update on each of each aspect of the applications and also
是应用程序各个方面的最新更新，并且
gave the early stage project builder a chance to show themselves to tell
给了早期项目建设者一个展示自己的机会
everyone that what is they are doing just like the demo days it's a open
每个人都知道他们在做什么，就像演示日一样，它是开放的
application from the public we have the form and everyone from the Twitter you
来自公众的申请，我们有表格，每个人都来自 Twitter
could see that everyone could apply for it and we have the evaluation from the
可以看到每个人都可以申请，我们有评估
tech from commercial side and the judges to select the project even if you didn't
商业方面的技术和评委来选择项目，即使你没有
have raised the fund yet or you are individual developers or the open source
尚未筹集资金或者您是个人开发者或开源者
contributors you could have the chance to present or show show the world what
您可以有机会向世界展示或展示什么
you are building. This is what EAG actually exists to support everyone to
你正在建造。这就是 EAG 的实际存在目的，以支持每个人
support all of you to have the chance to tell the world what you are doing. So
支持你们所有人有机会告诉世界你们在做什么。所以
there's also very important we have the core values here which is the EAG's main
还有一点非常重要，我们拥有核心价值观，这是 EAG 的主要目标
core values the first is openness it's open for everyone no matter you are the
核心价值观第一个是开放性，它对所有人开放，无论你是谁
institution you are the community builder you are the company you are the
机构 您是社区建设者 您是公司 您是
event organizer you are the founders and you are the PM PM or everyone of you it's
活动组织者，你是创始人，你是 PM PM 或者你们所有人
open for everyone and transparent because it's the governance the funding
对所有人开放且透明，因为治理就是资金
flows because it's an appeal the funding flows it's all transparent and the
流动，因为这是一个吸引力 资金流动 一切都是透明的
decentralization because it's not really a single entity or single
去中心化，因为它并不是真正的单一实体或单一
institutions it's the collaboration between every one of us and also public
机构，这是我们每个人以及公众之间的合作
goods first which is the main idea that EAG came from to support and have the
商品至上，这是EAG的主要理念，支持并拥有
sustainable way to support the public goods. So if we want to create a
支持公共产品的可持续方式。所以如果我们想创建一个
sustainable way to support the public goods the sustainable funding mechanism
支持公共产品的可持续方式 可持续的融资机制
is very important so EAG's funding is since it's an appeal effort yeah it's
非常重要，所以 EAG 的资金是因为它是一项呼吁努力，是的，它是
funding from mean from two aspects the first is a membership fee that's why for
资金来自两个方面，第一个是会员费，这就是为什么
EAG funding members maybe we're gonna announce that in this month or next
EAG 资助成员也许我们会在本月或下个月宣布
month the main funding is from the membership fee from the
月主要资金来自会员会费
institutions from the foundations from the VCs who want to contribute for the
来自基金会的机构 来自那些想要为这个项目做出贡献的风险投资家
ecosystem to help the Ethereum applications grow this is the first
生态系统帮助以太坊应用程序发展这是第一个
out of mainly from the membership fee the second is the stake in yield and for
主要来自会员费，第二个是收益的股份
lots of the long-term Ethereum supporters they willing to contribute
许多长期以太坊支持者愿意贡献
some of their stake in yield for the public for the sustainable funding
他们的部分收益为公众提供可持续资金
to support the applications ecosystem and what we actually we're gonna do
支持应用程序生态系统以及我们实际上要做的事情
this year and today we're also gonna be launched this kind of a program it's
今年和今天我们也将推出这样一个计划
called the 2020 global applications and the builders initiative for EAG is not
被称为 2020 年全球应用程序，而 EAG 的构建者倡议并不是
focused on in the unique region but it's globally and for this year it be
专注于独特的地区，但它是全球性的，今年它是
gonna be happen lots of the event can be happening in the emerging market just
很多事件都会发生在新兴市场
like the Africa
像非洲一样